One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
I grabbed hold, digging in my claws
te ni totte tsume o tateta
but the future
sono mirai wa
blurred together, colors running
nijimu iro ni kasunde mieta
A red that can swallow even summer's hues
natsu no iro mo nuritsubusu you na aka ni
bokura no koe kakikesareteiku you de
now attempts to blot out our voices
Move those halting feet of yours
tachidomaru sono ashi o fumidasou ze
Don't let stand the lies for show
misekake no uso yarisugosu yori
I'll give up countless mornings for my vows
nandome no asa chikai to hikikaeru yo
For the dream that we shared
bokura ga miteita yume
The Ebb and Flow of the Ages
Punk Hazard
26 years ago
I’m begging you, Vegapunk!
Research the Void Century with me!
This world has a darkness
too deep to ignore!
Conducting this research
requires knowledge from other fields as well.
Please, you’ve got to help me!
As you can plainly see,
I’m a Government scientist now.
I can’t provide you with any data.
How many times have you been caught?
You’re definitely on the Government’s radar!
You understand why
they’re keeping you alive, right?
They’re allowing you to roam free
so that they can root out your associates!
Pull back now.
So what of the “darkness”?
One cannot measure
the good and evil of the past!
A man who bore the name of “D”
was once killed in front of me.
It was out of the blue...
He grew up with me,
been by me since I was born...
He was my older brother.
My true name is Clou D. Clover.
A lie I told in that moment kept me alive.
H-He’s just my friend!
No one...
No one in this world should have to die
just for giving out their name!
There are historical records
being erased in secret...
I’m not going to help you,
and I’ll forget you ever told me that.
Be very careful out there.
Vegapunk!
I’ll do what I must to find the truth!
The voices of the past will be heard!
Punk Hazard
22 years ago
You hear about this?!
They say a Buster Call’s being issued
against Ohara in the West Blue!
I wanna witness the slaughter!
It’s about Clover, the archaeologist!
Looks like the World Government
finally got the goods on him!
No one’s ever gonna try
researching the Void Century ever again!
Now there’s an example,
if I ever saw one!
I’m begging you, Vegapunk!
Seems one Oharan kid
got away from the Buster Call!
Huh?!
They put a child this young
on the wanted list?
Surely you had time to escape...
Clover!
Did you all die just to preserve
this vast store of texts for the future?!
The absurdity of it all!
How crazy would you have to be,
daring to risk certain death
to continue your research?!
Someone once told me that
the voices of the past would be heard...
History is written by the victors.
The voices of the vanquished,
sunk deep beneath the sea, are barely audible.
But the truth, discovered
through great sacrifice...
has now been conveyed to the world.
I pray that this broadcast, up to this point,
has safely reached the ears of everyone.
Hey, what the hell’re we waitin’ for?!
Blast off already!
No, we can’t do that!
That horse-gramps is gonna attack us again!
And that’s exactly why we can’t leave!
I understand that this ship is equipped
with a booster capable of launching us one kilometer.
But if that monster slows down
our approach velocity even a bit,
we’ll be thrown off trajectory!
The wind’s blowing to the north!
A tailwind would reduce our lift,
and in my estimate,
the ship wouldn’t reach the water,
but crash into the ground instead!
In other words,
unless we get rid of that old geezer...
Whuh?!
Huh?!
Wha?!
Atlas?!
A giant boar, snake, bird, and robot?!
What’s going on, Vice Admiral Hound?!
Don’t know... I didn’t hear about any of this!
The giant Robo!
Is that an iron Giant?!
Joyboy...
I’m so happy... I get to see you again!
I’m talking to you!
Who’re you even talking about?
You go ahead.
Your enemy is my enemy.
Oh, I’m so happy...
I get to fight for you again...
Joyboy!
Amazing! You can talk!
Unless we crush it into tiny pieces...
Vegapunk’s speech will not end,
so it would seem.
Joyboy is in danger...
I must protect him!
Alright, guys!
Get this ship moving!
Hey! Is that thing on our side, Straw Hat?
Uhh, I dunno...
but he’s been saying
he’s gonna protect this Joyboy guy.
Who’s that?
“Saying”?!
I haven’t heard a thing!
Huh? Really?
Don’t just let them get away!
Maintain fire!
It would be foolish to hear the account of a war
that happened 900 years ago from only one side.
History must be approached
from multiple perspectives.
I wish I had more time.
But...
there are forces in motion
who can no longer be stopped!
It’s winding up!
It’s gonna shoot something!
Huh?
Whaaa?!
Watch out, Robo!
Aaahhh! Robo!
It’s a 900-year-old weapon!
Of course it didn’t work!
Peter! Crush it between your jaws!
Stop the broadcast!
There is no escaping me,
Kuma, Bonney!
Are you okay, Lilith?!
W-Why’d you do that to Lilith?!
Take care of Lilith!
Huh?
What?
What? Atlas?
Get airborne! I’ll take out
anything in your way!
What do you mean?!
Lilith’s access is cut off!
Only Atlas is left!
C’mon, Atlas!
Talk to us, what gives?!
Hey!
Zoro! Get Lilith inside!
On it!
Jinbe?!
Let’s go!
If we don’t act fast,
we’re going to regret it!
Brook! Do it!
As you wish, Zoro!
Coup de...
Burst!
The Sunny!
Hang on tight! Going down!
No!
Wait a second!
Are we even going to make it?!
You would sacrifice yourself...?
Nope... This service’s on the house.
Atlas!
Huh?!
We’re gonna make it...
all the way to the water!
No, you can’t do that to us, Atlas!
It’s not right!
Atlas is gone!
I’s the only Vegapunk in the world now!
No, not yet...
Not while Stella continues to babble on!
25 years ago,
the pirate Gol D. Roger at last completed
the world’s first circumnavigation.
And he and his crew
surely must have heard...
the purest voice of the past.
Wh-What?
What does he mean, “Gol D.”?
So,
I think everyone has realized by now,
but this is my projection for the future.
We will stop it at once!
Of course we will.
Oh no, no, no...
I’m all rusty now...
This is the right time, isn’t it?
Joyboy...
I’m gonna use it.
Fire!
Don’t let them get away!
Don't touch the claws! They're venomous!
It’s not like we want to...!
But he’s not letting up!
He just keeps comin’,
down to the very end!
Saturn!
If there’s one score I gotta settle...
It’s with you!
Distortion Future!
Pirate whelp!
You shall be first to perish!
You dare...!
Future Where...
I’m the Most Free!
Bonney?!
St. Saturn!
I’ll deal with you!
That’s it, Bonney! You do it!
One day, the memories of
the Void Century will surface!
In fact, the weapons that sank
all the continents in a man-made disaster...
still exist today, by someone’s design.
The machinations of history and fate
seem to insist upon the obliteration of...
those last descendants
of rare races!
Are you by chance a Buccaneer?!
What makes my blood so different
from other people?
I hear there was a “Land of the Gods”
atop the Red Line, long ago.
You’re a Lunarian, aren’t ya?
The Government’ll give you
a hundred million berries for info!
I gotta say, you’re creepy!
Look, she’s got three eyes!
It’s Nika!
What a pale imitation!
Saturn!
Ha, jerk!
Follow the Nikas!
How dare you do that to my dad?!
Your only options
are slavery and death.
Such is history’s decree.
How dare you do that to my mom?!
It was also I who conducted
drug experiments on your mother.
There’s no way that you guys are gods...
But gods do exist!
Bonney. It’s me, your mommy!
He’ll show up and save you!
And heroes are real, too!
I wish the three of us
could have lived together!
So many times I’ve thought
I’d rather die than be alone!
But no... I’m gonna live!
Because my parents...
wanted me to be happy!
There, there. Good girl!
Hey, Kumachi...
I’m so happy.
As am I.
Bonney...
Thank you...
for being born!
Damned insects, all of you!
Begone!
Liberation...
Nika Punch!
Should anything happen,
it is my sincere wish that
you all keep yourselves safe.
No matter what happens,
I believe in human wisdom!
I believe in science!
It’s been 25 years
since Roger died.
It’s been two years
since Whitebeard died.
But the fall of these legends
was merely the prologue of a new era!
As such...
those who refuse to buckle under
any and all suppression...
might indeed, quite ironically...
be the ones closest of all
to reaching the truth!
Sent ‘im flyin’!
Hey, Bonney!
Ya did good!
Look!
That’s your ship, right?!
The Sunny!
Falling—dying—help—
falling—dying—help!
Or no, perhaps Roger set it up
to happen that way.
You want my treasure?
Go ahead.
Find it!
Everything is right where I left it!
There is no guarantee that
the one Joyboy wanted will ultimately claim it.
Ray...
You’ll catch a cold.
Roger...
Emperor Blackbeard's hideout
Wasp's Nest, Pirate Island
Vegapunk!
I like the sound of what yer sayin’!
Aren’t the Commodore and
the rest of ‘em back yet?!
I can’t stand still!
Emperor Red-Haired's Ship
The Red Force
Boss! You’ve had one too many!
Shurrup! I ain’t drunk!
Boss!
Emperor Buggy's hideout
Emptee Bluffs Island
Chairman Buggy!
Eh?
We weren’t wrong!
Huh?
We didn’t realize what was at stake!
Your ambition has no limits!
Uhhh?
Buggy! Buggy!
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
Marine HQ
We must not let it fall into
the hands of pirates!
Perhaps if we found it first...
Then who’s gonna protect the civilians?
Buncha damned morons!
What was set in motion
now cannot be stopped.
The fate of the world now rests...
in the hands of the one who finds it!
The person who lays claim...
to the One Piece!
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop beep-beep-beep-bup-bop
piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipii pipopii, pipopiipii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep
piipapii papipo, piipapii
No, no, no, no, no, not feelin' it
no no no no no norenai
kobiritsuichatte mou odorenai
I'm all stiff, all outta dances
My head feels so good, 'f I get unlucky again
atama feel so good, mata unlucky demo
cola de fukitobase yowaki o
just gonna blow away the shy with a cola
Hey all you boys & girls! Looking good!
soko no boys & girls! omae ii yatsu
Hey all you boys & girls!
soko no boys & girls!
Update failed. I've had enough!
appudeto wa shippai kori gori
Wasn't it OK 'til yesterday?
kinou made nara seikai?
La la la la la la, run, run, run...
ran ran ran ran ran ran run run run
"Hiding yet?"
mou ii kai?
You ready yet, up for a dance
junbi wa douyo odoreru no?
bukkowareteru kono jidai
in this broken era?
"Come find us!"
mou ii yo!
Spread out from here, drop into the world
koko kara kakusan sekai e drop
Let loose on the stage of freedom and liberation
jiyuu to kaihou no stage e
Those rising heads're punks!!!!!! No way!!!
wakiagaru atama ga punk!!!!!! no way!!!
Sick of waitin', goof off and dance
matenaiyo fuzaketa dance
Dopamine spilling over
afuredasu dopamine
The lonely singing in unity
kodoku ga tsudoi utau koushin
Bip-bip-bip-bup-bup-bup-bup-bupping
pipipi papapapapatteru
Can't can't can't count me out yet
mada mada mada horobinai
There's some stranger waving me over
shiranai dareka ga temaneki da
Smilin' so wide that it can't be real
uso mitai ni waratteru